[{
        "question": "Which of the following is correct about PHP?",
        "answers": [{
                "text": " PHP is a recursive acronym for PHP: Hypertext Preprocessor.",
                "value": "0"
            },
            {
                "text": "PHP is a server side scripting language that is embedded in HTML.",
                "value": "1"
            },
            {
                "text": "It is used to manage dynamic content, databases, session tracking, even build entire e-commerce sites.",
                "value": "2"
            },
            {
                "text": "All of the above.",
                "value": "3"
            }
        ],
        "correct_answer": "3"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of the following type of variables are named and indexed collections of other values?",
        "answers": [{
                "text": "String",
                "value": "0"
            },
            {
                "text": "Array",
                "value": "1"
            },
            {
                "text": "Objects",
                "value": "2"
            },
            {
                "text": "Resources",
                "value": "3"
            }
        ],
        "correct_answer": "1"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of the following magic constant of PHP returns class method name?",
        "answers": [{
                "text": "_METHOD_",
                "value": "0"
            },
            {
                "text": " _FILE_",
                "value": "1"
            },
            {
                "text": "_FUNCTION_",
                "value": "2"
            },
            {
                "text": "_CLASS_",
                "value": "3"
            }
        ],
        "correct_answer": "0"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of the following function sorts an array in reverse order?",
        "answers": [{
                "text": "rsort()",
                "value": "0"
            },
            {
                "text": " sort()",
                "value": "1"
            },
            {
                "text": "shuffle()",
                "value": "2"
            },
            {
                "text": "reset()",
                "value": "3"
            }
        ],
        "correct_answer": "0"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of the following function opens a file?",
        "answers": [{
                "text": "fopen()",
                "value": "0"
            },
            {
                "text": "fread()",
                "value": "1"
            },
            {
                "text": "filesize()",
                "value": "2"
            },
            {
                "text": "file_exist()",
                "value": "3"
            }
        ],
        "correct_answer": "0"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of the following is used to get cookies?",
        "answers": [{
                "text": "getcookie() function",
                "value": "0"
            },
            {
                "text": "$_COOKIE variable",
                "value": "1"
            },
            {
                "text": "isset() function",
                "value": "2"
            },
            {
                "text": "None of the above.",
                "value": "3"
            }
        ],
        "correct_answer": "1"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of the following provides content type of the uploaded file in PHP?",
        "answers": [{
                "text": "$_FILES['file']['tmp_name']",
                "value": "0"
            },
            {
                "text": "$_FILES['file']['name']",
                "value": "1"
            },
            {
                "text": "$_FILES['file']['size']",
                "value": "2"
            },
            {
                "text": "$_FILES['file']['type']",
                "value": "3"
            }
        ],
        "correct_answer": "3"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of the following method connect a MySql database using PHP?",
        "answers": [{
                "text": "mysql_connect()",
                "value": "0"
            },
            {
                "text": "mysql_query()",
                "value": "1"
            },
            {
                "text": "mysql_close()",
                "value": "2"
            },
            {
                "text": "None of the above",
                "value": "3"
            }
        ],
        "correct_answer": "0"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of the following method of Exception class retrieve the error message when error occured?",
        "answers": [{
                "text": "getMessage()",
                "value": "0"
            },
            {
                "text": "getCode()",
                "value": "1"
            },
            {
                "text": "getFile()",
                "value": "2"
            },
            {
                "text": "getLine()",
                "value": "3"
            }
        ],
        "correct_answer": "0"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of the following is correct about constants vs variables in PHP?",
        "answers": [{
                "text": "There is no need to write a dollar sign ($) before a constant, where as in Variable one has to write a dollar sign.",
                "value": "0"
            },
            {
                "text": "Constants cannot be defined by simple assignment, they may only be defined using the define() function.",
                "value": "1"
            },
            {
                "text": "Both of the above.",
                "value": "2"
            },
            {
                "text": "None of the above.",
                "value": "3"
            }
        ],
        "correct_answer": "2"
    }
]